# Salsabil Tarek

#### Front-End Developer

With 3 years experience in building responsive websites with HTML,CSS,Bootstrap,SASS,JavaScript,JQuery,Pug and frameworks like Angular 8, React.js in agile environment using git as version control, Also have experience in CMS like "Wordpress, Joomla!". I have Knowledge about clean code and care to use it in my Work.

🔀 salsabil.tarek55@gmail.com

Riyadh, Saudi arabia

in linkedin.com/in/salsabil-tarek-630088a6

+966 581734214

salsabil55.github.io/profile/

github.com/salsabil55

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Front-End Developer

Freelance

2022 - Present

Riyadh, Saudi Arabia

## Front-End Developer

DafHolding

10/2019 - 06/2021 maadi,Egypt

## **SKILLS**



## Front-End Developer

Pharous

08/2018 - 10/2019

Alexandria, Egypt

## **Wordpress Developer**

OneHoster

02/2017 - 07/2018 Alexandria, Egypt

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Front End Web Development Professional Udacity

Web Development using Nodejs and Angular

National Telecommunication Institute (NTI)

Web Development using PHP, MySQL and Laravel

National Telecommunication Institute (NTI)

## **EDUCATION**

## Computer Science

Faculty of Science

09/2012 - 06/2015 Alexandria, Very Good

### **LANGUAGES**

Arabic

English

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Professional Working Proficiency

### **INTERESTS**

Motion Graphic

**Animations** 

Graphic design